She will transform us
Gaia is a horror, fantasy, drama film directed by Jaco Bouwer.
In the depths of an ancient forest, something has been growing.
Something older than humanity itself, and perhaps greater too.
When a park ranger discovers a man and his son living wild, she
stumbles onto a secret that is about to change the world.
Gabi, played by Monique Rockman.
Barend, played by Carel Nel.
Stefan, played by Alex van Dyk.
Winston, played by Anthony Oseyemi.
Gaia is a 2021 South African horror thriller film produced and
directed by Jaco Bouwer from a screenplay by Tertius Kapp.
It stars Monique Rockman, Carel Nel, Alex van Dyk, and Anthony Oseyemi.
It had its world premiere at South by Southwest in
the United States on 16 March 2021.
It had a limited theatrical release in the country on 18 June 2021, prior
to a video on demand release the week after, by Decal.
The film received positive reviews from critics, with
praise directed at the film's visuals.
The film explores themes of canoe, forest, forest ranger, assimilation, fungus.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.